Guide to the Football Records, 1922-[ongoing]
Duke University. University Archives
Football records 1922-[ongoing]
Duke University. University Archives
Duke University. Sports Information Office.
83.0 linear feet Extent: about 83,300 Items
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. The collection includes clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, programs and press brochures/media guides about the football team at Duke University. The material ranges in date from 1922-ongoing.
uaftball
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Online Items
Items from this collection have been digitized and are available in: Duke Football Programs - Duke Digital Collections
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Provenance
The Football Records were received by the University Archives as transfers over time.
Historical Note
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. For many years, the SI Office has maintained records, photographs and other material about Duke athletic teams.
Collection Overview
The collection includes clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, programs and press brochures/media guides about the football team at Duke University. There are files regarding the freshman football team, specifically the yearly fundraising game played between Duke and the University of North Carolina freshman football teams to raise money for cerebral palsy research. The material ranges in date from 1922-ongoing.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Duke University. Sports Information Office; Duke University -- Football -- History -- 20th century; Duke University -- Sports
Related Material
Non-Revenue Sports Records.
Duke University Archives.
Basketball Records.
Duke University Archives.
Athletic Dept. Records.
Duke University Archives.
Scrapbooks.
Duke University Archives.
Photograph Collection.
Duke University Archives.
Dean Wright Collection.
Duke University Archives.
Edmund M. Cameron Records.
Duke University Archives.
Photographic Negative Collection.
Duke University Archives.
Chanticleer Photograph Collection.
Duke University Archives.
Athletics Reference Collection.
Duke University Archives.
Athletic Council Records.
Duke University Archives.
Athletics Department Football and Basketball Game Film and Video Collection
http://library.duke.edu/uarchives/holdings/film/sportsfilms.html
Contents of Collection
- Yearly Files, 1931-1989, 82 Boxes
  The yearly files contain clippings, scores, statistics, rosters, programs, game files and game-related information.
  - 1931-1933 (Box 1)
  - 1933-1935 (Box 2)
  - 1935-1937 (Box 3)
  - 1938-1939 (Box 4)
  - 1940-1942 (Box 5)
  - 1943-1946 (Box 6)
  - 1947-1949 (Box 7)
  - 1949-1952 (Box 8)
  - 1953-1955 (Box 9)
  - 1956-1958 (Box 10)
  - 1959-1960 (Box 11)
  - 1961-1962 (Box 12)
  - 1963 (Box 13)
  - 1963 (Box 14)
  - 1964 (Box 15)
  - 1964 (Box 16)
  - 1965 (Box 17)
  - 1965, 1966 (Box 18)
  - 1966 (Box 19)
  - 1966, 1967 (Box 20)
  - 1967 (Box 21)
  - 1967 (Box 22)
  - 1967, 1968 (Box 23)
  - 1968 (Box 24)
  - 1968, 1969 (Box 25)
  - 1969 (Box 26)
  - 1969 (Box 27)
  - 1969, 1970 (Box 28)
  - 1970, 1971 (Box 29)
  - 1971 (Box 30)
  - 1971, 1972 (Box 31)
  - 1972 (Box 32)
  - 1973 (Box 33)
  - 1973, 1974 (Box 34)
  - 1974, 1975 (Box 35)
  - 1975 (Box 36)
  - 1975, 1976 (Box 37)
  - 1976, 1977 (Box 38)
  - 1977, 1978 (Box 39)
  - 1978 (Box 40)
  - 1979 (Box 41)
  - 1979, 1980 (Box 42)
  - 1980 (Box 43)
  - 1981 (Box 44)
  - 1981, 1982 (Box 45)
  - 1982 (Box 46)
  - 1982, 1983 (Box 47)
  - 1983 (Box 48)
  - 1984 (Box 49)
  - 1984, 1985 (Box 50)
  - 1985 (Box 51)
  - 1985, 1986 (Box 52)
  - 1986, 1987 (Box 53)
  - 1987 (Box 54)
  - 1987, 1988 (Box 55)
  - 1988 (Box 56)
  - 1988, 1989 (Box 57)
  - 1989 (Box 58)
  - 1989-1990 (Box 86)
  - 1990-1991 (Box 87)
  - 1991 (Box 88)
  - 1991-1992 (Box 89)
  - 1992 (Box 90)
  - 1993 (Box 91)
  - 1993-1994 (Box 92)
  - 1994 (Box 93)
  - 1994-1995 (Box 94)
  - 1995 (Box 95)
  - 1995-1996 (Box 96)
  - 1996 (Box 97)
  - 1996-1997 (Box 98)
  - 1997 (Box 99)
  - 1997 (Box 100)
  - 1998 (Box 101)
  - 1999 (Box 102)
  - 1999 (Box 103)
  - 2000 (Box 104)
  - 2000 (Box 105)
  - 2001 (Box 106)
  - 2001-2002 (Box 107)
  - 2002 (Box 108)
  - 2002 (Box 109)
- Game Programs, 1922-[ongoing], 30 Boxes
  - 1922-1935 (Box 59)
  - 1936-1939 (Box 60)
  - 1940-1943 (Box 61)
  - 1944-1947 Oct. 25 (Box 62)
  - 1947 Nov. 8-1950 Oct. 28 (Box 63)
  - 1950 Nov. 4-1952 Nov. 22 (Box 64)
  - 1953 Sept. 19-1954 (Box 65)
  - 1955-1956 (Box 66)
  - 1957 Sept. 21-1959 Sept. 26 (Box 67)
  - 1959 Oct. 3-1961 Oct. 28 (Box 68)
  - 1961 Nov. 4-1965 Oct. 16 (Box 69)
  - 1965 Nov. 28-1970 Nov. 7 (Box 70)
  - 1970 Nov. 14-1974 Nov. 16 (Box 71)
  - 1975 Sept. 20-1980 Nov. 8 (Box 72)
  - 1981 Oct. 3-1984 Nov. 24 (Box 73)
  - 1985 Sept. 7-1987 Nov. 14 (Box 74)
  - 1988 Sept. 17-1990 Sept. 22 (Box 75)
  - 1990 Sept. 29-1991 Sept. 7 (Box 76)
  - 1991 Sept. 14-1992 Sept. 5 (Box 77)
  - 1992 Sept. 12-1993 Sept. 4 (Box 78)
  - 1993 Sept. 11-1994 Sept. 15 (Box 110)
  - 1994 Sept. 24-1995 Sept. 9 (Box 111)
  - 1995 Sept. 16-1996 Sept. 9 (Box 112)
  - 1996 Sept. 14-1997 Sept. 13 (Box 113)
  - 1997 Sept. 20-1998 Sept. 19 (Box 114)
  - 1998 Sept. 26-1999 Oct. 16 (Box 115)
  - 1999 Oct. 30-2000 Nov. (Box 116)
  - 2000 Nov. 11-2001 Oct. 27 (Box 117)
  - 2001 Nov. 3-2002 Nov. 23 (Box 118)
  - N.C. All-State Charity Game, 1931; Duke vs. Davidson, 1931; 1996 Nov. 9 (Box 119)
- Press Brochures/Media Guides, 1949-[ongoing], 6 Boxes
  The date ranges below do not reflect a complete set.
  - 1979, 1949, 1951-1954 [bound football programs] c.2 (Box 79)
  - 1940-1972 (Box 80)
  - 1972-1985 (Box 81)
  - 1986-1998 (Box 82)
  - 1999-2006 (Box 83)
  - 2007-[ongoing] (Box 84)
- Duplicates, 1 Box
  - 1940-1989 c.2 (incomplete) (Box 85)
  - 1990-2006 c. 2 (incomplete) (Box 120)